(Penny:)There you go.
(Leonard:)Are you sure
this is right?
(Penny:)Yeah, just tuck that
part in your pants;  you'll be fine.
Okay, let's go smooch some
rich, wrinkled tochis.
(Penny:)Oh, Howard, I can't believe
Bernadette let you go
(Penny:)to a fancy party
wearing a dickey.
(Howard:)Excuse me, my girlfriend
doesn't pick out my clothes.
(Howard:)My mother does.
(Leonard:)Oh. We should
get going.
(Howard:)What about Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Sheldon is not going.
(Leonard:)Really? What do we tell Siebert?
(Sheldon:)Tell him Dr. Cooper feels
that the best use of his time
(Sheldon:)is to employ his rare
and precious mental faculties
(Sheldon:)to tear the mask off nature
and stare at the face of God.
(Penny:)Sheldon, it's Saturday night,
you'll be doing laundry.
(Sheldon:)Don't tell him that,
tell him the mask thing.